Guide to the Harry Weinberger Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Original accession, 1915-1943
  - The God of Vengeance
    The material in this section relates both to Weinberger's defense on the obscenity charge and to his duties as manager of the play. Through industrious letter writing, Weinberger mobilized a great deal of publicity and support for The God of Vengeance from prominent theatrical, social and religious leaders. This section includes letters from Roger N. Baldwin, Zachariah Chafee, Frank Crane, Felix Frankfurter, John H. Holmes, Fannie Hurst, Percy MacKaye, Elmer Rice, Stephen S. Wise, and many others.
    - Correspondence
      - A-Y, 1923-1926 (Box 23, Folder 12-21)
      - Abrahams, Israel (1), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Actors' Equity Association (1) (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Adams, H. S. (1), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - American Civil Liberties Union
        See: Baldwin, Roger, box 24, folder 3
      - American Fund for Public Service
      - American Magazine (6), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Americanism Protective League (3), 1924 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Asch, Sholom (7), 1923, 1925 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Authors' League of America (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Baldwin, Roger N. (36), 1924-1925 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Bloom, I. Mortimer (2), 1923, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Brandeis, Louis D. (2), 1925 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Brisbane, Arthur (5), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Butler, Nicholas M. (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Cane, Meville H. (7), 1923-1924 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Chafee, Zacariah (13), 1924-1925 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - The Civic Club (1), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Conboy, Martin (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Conway, William O. (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Crane, Frank (6), 1923, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Crump, Richard (4), 1925 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - DeSilver, Albert (1), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Dintefass, Mark M. (4), 1923, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Dix, Mark H. (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Ernst, Morris L. (8), 1923, 1925 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Erwin, Charles W. (2), 1925 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Fitzgerald, Eleanor M. (9), 1923-1924 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Flynn, Elizabeth G. (10), 1924-1925 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Frankfurter, Felix (7), 1924 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - The Freeman (5), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Gilman, George H. (15), 1923-1926 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Gladstone, Joseph (3), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - God of Vengeance: correspondence relating to trial and appeal (78), 1923-1925 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Goldberg, Isaac (8), 1924, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Granick, Alexander (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Greil, Cecil L. (1), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Hand, Learned (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Harby, M.E. (6), 1925 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Harris, Maurice H. (6), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Holmes, John H. (27), 1923-1926 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Hurst, Fannie (4), 1923-1924 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Hylan, John F. (4), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Jaffe, Sam (4), 1923, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Jewish Daily Forward
        See: Vladeck, B.C., box 25, folder 8
      - Kahn, Otto H. (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Kauser, Alice (60), 1923-1926 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Knoblanch, Mary (3), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Kopp, Harry (4), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Krass, Nathan (8), 1923, 1925-1926 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - MacKaye, Percy (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Markham, Edwin (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Marshall, Louis (3), 1923-1924 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Mencken, H. L. (7), 1924, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - The Nation (22), 1923-1926 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Neumann, Henry (6), 1923-1924, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - New York American (6), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - New York Call (9), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - New York Evening Post (3), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - New York Globe (9), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - New York Sunday World (2), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - New York Times (24), 1923-1925 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - New York Tribune (1), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - New York World (3), 1923 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Overstreet, Harry A. (6), 1923, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Perls, Edwin A. (4), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Perls, L.T. (1), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Pollack, Walter (4), 1924 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Pollock, Channing (3), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Quinn, John (6), 1923-1924 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Rice, Elmer (11), 1923-1925 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Rosenberg, James N. (10), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Ross, Arthur L. (4), 1923-1925 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Schildkraut, Joseph (2), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Schildkraut, Rudolph (9), 1923, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Schroeder, Theodore (13), 1923-1925 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Schulman, Samuel (4), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Seabury, Samuel (17), 1924-1926 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Selwyn and Co. (15), 1923-1924, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Smith, Alfred E. (2), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Stratford Co. (27), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Todd, Helen (3), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Trosk, George (4), 1924 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Untermyer, Samuel (5), 1923-1924, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Van Doren, Carl (3), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Vladeck, B. Charney (26), 1923-1926 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Voorhees, W. A. (5), 1926 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Waldman, Louis (2), 1924 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Wise, Stephen S. (14), 1923, 1925-1926 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Wormser, I. Maurice (16), 1923-1925 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Young, Arthur (3), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Legal papers, 1923 March-1925, undated (Box 25, Folder 10-15)
    - Notes (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Actors' contacts, addresses, etc. (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
    - Financial materials (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
      Box office statements, payroll, expense lists, checks, and receipts
    - Publicity materials (Box 26, Folder 8-10)
  - Goldman, Emma
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, clippings, and miscellaneous papers. Weinberger was a close friend and advisor of the noted anarchist and radical Goldman. He represented her in several court cases and in some business matters. Weinberger was also an advisor of Goldman's associate Alexander Berkman. Material relating to both Goldman and Berkman is filed in this section.
    Weinberger's relationship with Goldman spanned more than twenty years. He defended her in 1916 against a charge of distributing literature relating to birth control. In 1917, Goldman and Berkman were indicted in the United States District Court of New York for interfering with the execution of the Selective Service Act. They acted as their own lawyers, with Weinberger as an advisor. Goldman was sentenced to two years in the United States Penitentiary at Jefferson City, Missouri, and Berkman was sentenced to two years in the United States Penitentiary at Atlanta, Georgia. Charging no fee, Weinberger appealed to the United States Supreme Court on the basis that the draft law violated the thirteenth amendment. The Supreme Court declared the draft law constitutional and affirmed the convictions of Goldman and Berkman. They began their prison terms in 1918.
    Weinberger corresponded with Goldman at great length while she was serving her term in the Jefferson City Prison. These letters touch on many subjects including Goldman's situation and the cases of other radicals in America. She also wrote about prison conditions and her friendship with fellow prisoner Kate Richards O'Hare.
    Upon their release from prison, Goldman and Berkman, both professed anarchists, were held for deportation. Weinberger unsuccessfully tried to prove that Goldman was a citizen due to her marriage to Jacob A. Kersner. Goldman and Berkman were deported to Russia in December, 1919 on the S.S. Buford. They later fled to Latvia and then to Germany.
    While Goldman was in exile in Germany, Weinberger attempted to straighten out a series of mishaps that had befallen her manuscript, "My Two Years in Russia." This manuscript was eventually published as My Disillusionment in Russia and My Further Disillusionment in Russia. There is extensive correspondence with Goldman, Clinton T. Brainard, and Doubleday, Page and Company in regard to these books.
    Though widely separated by her deportation, Weinberger kept in fairly close touch with Goldman. She continued to write him, informing him of her travels and her activities in the Spanish Civil War shortly before her death.
    The material in this section, after the correspondence, is broken into several sections as follows:
    A) Emma Goldman: This section contains legal papers relating to Goldman's book, published as My Disillusionment in Russia and My Further Disillusionment in Russia. Also filed in this section are newspaper clippings on Berkman and Goldman and copies of the newspaper serialization of My Disillusionment in Russia.
    B) Alexander Berkman: Copies of the magazine The Blast, published and edited by Berkman are filed in this section.
    C) New York vs. Emma Goldman: This section contains material relating to Goldman's 1916 trial for distributing birth control information.
    D) United States vs. Emma Goldman and Alexander Berkman: Material relating to Goldman and Berkman's 1917 trial for interfering with the execution of the Selective Service Act is filed in this section. This includes a two volume set of the stenographer's minutes of the court proceedings. Also contained in this section are documents concerning Weinberger's attempts to prove that Goldman was a United States citizen.
    E) A. Berkman vs. The New York Produce Exchange Bank and E. Goldman vs. The New York Produce Exchange Bank: Legal papers concerning the above cases are contained in this section. Weinberger charged that the bank had no right to turn over Goldman and Berkman's funds to the United States Marshall.
    F) California vs. Alexander Berkman: This section contains material concerning the extradition of Alexander Berkman to California where he was charged with first degree murder in connection with the Tom Mooney case. Proceedings were dropped by the district attorney in San Francisco because the United States Attorney desired to retain Berkman until the case of the United States vs. Emma Goldman and Alexander Berkman had been decided.
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, unidentified (335), 1916-1920, 1922-1925, 1931, 1936, 1939, undated (Box 27, Folder 1-13)
      - Abbott, Leonard D. (15), 1917, 1919, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - American Civil Liberties Union (11), 1933 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Association of the Bar (5), 1917-1918 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Baldwin, Roger N. (10), 1917-1919, 1922, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Ballentine, Henry (3), 1923 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Ballentine, Stella (31), 1918-1919, 1922, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Berkman, Alexander (70), 1916-1919, 1921-1922 (Box 27, Folder 17-18)
      - Berman, Morris (3), 1918-1919 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Blackwell, Alice Stone (2), 1918-1919 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Brainard, Clinton T. (38), 1923-1924 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Brandeis, Louis D. (5), 1917-1919 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Brandt and Kirkpatrick (14), 1923-1924 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Cassidy, W. T. (3), 1918 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Castleton, Samuel M. (16), 1919-1920 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Clemens, Addie (3), 1919 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Cohn, Michael A. (24), 1917-1920, 1923-1925 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Commins, Louis H. (1), 1919 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Commins, Saxe (10), 1919 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Creel, George (10), 1917-1918 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Dalzell, George W. (2), 1919 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Darrow, Clarence (3), 1917 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - The Day (16), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Doubleday, Page and Co. (101), 1923-1926 (Box 28, Folder 5-7)
      - Eastman, Max (2), 1917-1918 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Ellis, Havelock
        See: Goldman, Emma (1925 Feb 27), box 29, folder 6
      - Ewing, H. W. (3), 1918 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Fitzgerald, M. Eleanor (17), 1917-1920, 1923-1925, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Freie Arbeiter Stimme (14), 1924-1925, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Goldman, Emma (198), 1915-1919 (Box 28, Folder 10-21)
      - Goldman, Emma (231), 1920-1926, 1931-1934, 1936-1939, undated (Box 29, Folder 1-10)
      - Grosser, David and Philip B. (5), 1917-1918 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Hall, Bolton (4), 1917 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Harris, Frank (9), 1917-1919, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Harvey, Alice D. (5), 1936 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Hiss, Alger (1), 1938 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Inglis, Agnes (17), 1917-1919, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Jefferson City Prison
        See: Missouri State Prison Board, box 29, folder 21
      - Jewish Daily Forward (4), 1918, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Jones, J. Gordon (55), 1917-1919 (Box 29, Folder 14-15)
      - Kelly, Harry (1), 1919 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Kennan, Ellen A. (6), 1918, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Kiefer, Daniel (14), 1917-1920 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Knopf, Alfred A. (5), 1924 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - LaFollette, Robert M. (2), 1917 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - McClure Newspaper Syndicate
        See: Brainard, Clinton T., box 27, folder 20
      - McKenzie, Edwin V. (8), 1918-1919 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - McNutt, Maxwell (10), 1917-1918 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Marshall, Louis (4), 1917 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Mencken, H. L. (4), 1924 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Merlin, M. J. (8), 1918-1919 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Milholland, John E. (4), 1917 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Minor, Robert (2), 1917 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Missouri State Prison Board (22), 1918-1920 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Mooney, Tom (7), 1918, 1935-1936 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Nathanson, William (3), 1917 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - The Nation (5), 1924 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - National Civil Liberties Bureau
        See: American Civil Liberties Union, box 27, folder 14
      - Nelson, Walter M. (4), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - New York State District Attorney (7), 1917 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Novoye Russkoye Slovo (14), 1923-1924 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - O'Connell, Daniel (7), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Older, Fremont (2), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - O'Neill, Harry F. (24), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Reedy, William M. (8), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Rifkind, Albert J. (2), 1917 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Rimer, Minnie (8), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Rosenberg, Arthur L. (1), 1917 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Schroeder, Theodore (4), 1917, 1919 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Shay, Felix (5), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Shelwalter, Joseph D. (3), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Sinclair, Upton (5), 1918, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Sloan, Anna (13), 1917 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Stern and Rubens (6), 1923-1924 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Stowe, L. Beecher (Box 30)
        See: Doubleday, Page and Co., box 28, folders 5-7
      - Sullivan and Sullivan and Theodore J. Roche (7), 1918 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Tresca, Carlo (3), 1938 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Tumulty, Joseph P. (3), 1919 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - United Hebrew Trades (6), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - U.S. Army (2), 1916 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - U.S. Department of Justice (13), 1917-1919 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - U.S. Department of Justice, Attorney General (27) (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - U.S. Department of Justice, Solicitor General (52), 1917-1919, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - U.S. Department of Justice, Superintendent of Prisons (14) (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (129), 1917-1920 (Box 30, Folder 14-16)
      - U.S. Department of State (2), 1919, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - U.S. Navy (2), 1916 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - U.S. Post Office (22), 1917, 1919, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - U.S. Penitentiary, Atlanta, Georgia (39), 1917, 1919, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - U.S. Supreme Court, Clerk (56), 1917-1919 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - U.S. Treasury Department (7), 1917-1920 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - U.S. War Department (1) (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Van Valkenburgh, W.S. (4), 1925-1926 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Walsh, Frank P. (7), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Watson, Thomas E. (36), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Whitman, Charles S. (15), 1917 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Wood, Charles E. S. (10), 1917-1918 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - A) Emma Goldman
      - 1923, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1917, 1919, 1922, 1924-1925, 1928, 1939, undated (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - B) Alexander Berkman
      - The Blast, 1916-1917 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Legal papers
      - C) New York vs. Emma Goldman, 1916 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - D) United States vs. Emma Goldman and Alexander Berkman
        - 1884, 1907-1909, 1917-1918 (Box 31, Folder 9-16)
        - 1919-1920, undated (Box 32, Folder 1-5)
        - Stenographer's minutes of U.S. vs. E. Goldman and A. Berkman (2 volumes) (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
        - Notes (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
      - E) A. Berkman vs. The New York Produce Exchange Bank, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
      - F) California vs. A. Berkman
        - 1917 June-Nov, 1919-1920, undated (Box 33, Folder 6-9)
        - Notes (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Gollomb, Joseph
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes concerning Liveright Publishing Corporation vs. Joseph Gollomb, 1939-1940. Weinberger was attorney for Gollomb in a dispute over the royalties for Gollomb's book Armies of Spies.
    - Correspondence
      - Gollomb, Joseph (4), 1940 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Koenig, Bachner, and Koenig (5), 1939-1940 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Liveright Publishing Corporation (1), 1939 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - The Macmillan Company (2), 1939 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Legal papers, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Gonzales, Jesus
    See: Rangel, Jesus M., box 43, folder 1
  - Goodman, Jacob
    See: Aziz, Demitri, box 3, folders 23-25
  - Grecia, Rogelio
    See: Fernandez, Jose Ramon, box 21, folders 15-16
  - Grob, Sylvia (1), 1939 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    The papers consist of letters and legal papers. Weinberger drew up wills for Sylvia and Bernard Grob.
  - Group Theatre, The
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes concerning Group Theatre vs. Producing Associates Inc., 1932-1935. Weinberger was retained by Cheryl Crawford to represent the Group Theatre in a dispute with Producing Associates Inc. The dispute involved the sale of the motion picture rights to the play Success Story.
    - Correspondence
      - Bickerton, Joseph P. (4), 1933-1934 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Brandt and Brandt Dramatic Department (2), 1933 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - The Group Theatre, Inc. (10), 1933-1935 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Langer, Lawrence (5), 1933 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - McKaig, Alexander (1), 1933 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Producing Associates, Inc. (5), 1932-1933 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Theatre Guild (1), 1933 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Weinberger, Milton R. (1), 1933 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Legal papers, 1932-1933 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Notes (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Hamilton Memorial
    The papers consist of letters, notes, clippings, and miscellaneous papers. Weinberger was chairman of a New York County Lawyers Association committee that sponsored a memorial tablet to Alexander Hamilton. Hamilton was the Philadelphia lawyer who defended John Peter Zenger in 1735 against a charge of malicious libel and thus helped establish the freedom of the press in America.
    - Correspondence
      - A-H, K-P, R-V, Y-Z (186), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 1-5)
      - Abbott, Leonard D. (4), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Allen, Henry J. (3), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - American Bar Association Journal (8), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - American Civil Liberties Union (9), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Baldwin, Roger
        See: American Civil Liberties Union, box 34, folder 7
      - Beck, James M. (4), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Borah, William E. (12), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Boston, Charles A.
        See: New York County Lawyers Association, President, box 34, folders 14-15
      - Breed, William C. (6), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Clark, A. Mortimer (5), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Connor, John M., Jr. (3), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Davis, John W. (2), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - DeCasseres, Benjamin (4), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Dennett, Mary Ware (1), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Evans, Barle W. (1), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Garrigues, Ellen (4) (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - General Bronze Corporation (11), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Gilbert, Cass (3), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Goldman, Mayer C. (5), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Hennessy, Charles (3), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Hughes, William J. (2), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Library of Congress (7), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - McCracken, Robert T. (9), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Morris, Robert C. (8), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - New York County Lawyers Association, Librarian (17), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - New York County Lawyers Association, President (127), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 14-15)
      - New York County Lawyers Association, Secretary (17), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - New York County Lawyers Association, Treasurer (16), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - O'Leary, Arthur T. (3), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Philadelphia Bar Association (9), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Phillips, Nathaniel (11), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Pinochet, Gifford (1), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Schroeder, Theodore (5), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Seabury, Samuel (2), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Sudell, Harold (2), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Weigle, W. Harold (6), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Williams, Henry D. (9), 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Wise, Stephen S. (3), 1934 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1934, undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets and photographs (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Notes (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Hecht, Charles (1), 1933 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    The papers consist of letter and notes concerning Charles Hecht vs. Trenton Trust Company, 1933. Weinberger was retained by Hecht to file a suit against the Trenton Trust Company.
  - Hued, Alejandro
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes. Weinberger represented Hued in negotiations with the Bureau of Immigration to allow his entrance into the United States.
    - Correspondence
      - Hued, Alejandro (2), 1919 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Nehme, Elias (1), 1919 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (2), 1919 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Legal papers, 1919 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Itzickson, Jacob